<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>https://gen.polyb.io/</id><title>PolyGen Game</title><subtitle>The PolyGen game using RFID cards to capture devices</subtitle> <updated>2026-01-03T16:46:21+00:00</updated> <author> <name>Michael Turner</name> <uri>https://gen.polyb.io/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://gen.polyb.io/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="https://gen.polyb.io/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2026 Michael Turner </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>39C3 Game Results</title><link href="https://gen.polyb.io/posts/39C3results/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="39C3 Game Results" /><published>2025-12-31T14:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2026-01-03T16:45:54+00:00</updated> <id>https://gen.polyb.io/posts/39C3results/</id> <content src="https://gen.polyb.io/posts/39C3results/" /> <author> <name>Michael Turner</name> </author> <category term="39C3" /> <summary> 39C3 is over and so we must analyse the stats from the PolyGen game! General Stats Total players: 1,681 Total players scoring over 1,000 points: 1,134 Total players score: 11,392,010 Total unit captures: 30,294 Total unit visits: 33,164 Total output boosts: 2,899 Players who set a codename: 257 Players too lazy to set a codename: 1,424 Maximum Units Online: 36 Units Faile... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>PolyGen at 39C3</title><link href="https://gen.polyb.io/posts/39C3/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PolyGen at 39C3" /><published>2025-12-25T11:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2025-12-27T17:30:03+00:00</updated> <id>https://gen.polyb.io/posts/39C3/</id> <content src="https://gen.polyb.io/posts/39C3/" /> <author> <name>Michael Turner</name> </author> <category term="39C3" /> <summary> Polybius Biotech are pleased to announce the deployment of PolyGen portable fusion generates across the 39C3 event site. How to play To play you simply need an RFID card. Most cards will work, although anything that generates a dynamic identifier such as mobile phones and some bank cards will not work. Your objective is to keep as many of the units aligned to your team as possible. You can... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>WAMP2025 Game Results</title><link href="https://gen.polyb.io/posts/wamp2025results/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WAMP2025 Game Results" /><published>2025-09-02T15:00:00+01:00</published> <updated>2025-09-02T23:10:20+01:00</updated> <id>https://gen.polyb.io/posts/wamp2025results/</id> <content src="https://gen.polyb.io/posts/wamp2025results/" /> <author> <name>Michael Turner</name> </author> <category term="WAMP2025" /> <summary> WAMP 2025 is over and so we must analyse the stats from this year’s PolyGen game! General Stats Total players: 130 Total players scoring over 1,000 points: 103 Total players score: 3,471,709 Total unit captures: 9,552 Total unit visits: 8,814 Total output boosts: 903 Players who set a codename: 56 Players too lazy to set a codename: 74 Maximum Units Online: 17 Units Faile... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>PolyGen at WAMP</title><link href="https://gen.polyb.io/posts/wamp/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PolyGen at WAMP" /><published>2025-08-29T12:00:00+01:00</published> <updated>2025-08-29T12:00:00+01:00</updated> <id>https://gen.polyb.io/posts/wamp/</id> <content src="https://gen.polyb.io/posts/wamp/" /> <author> <name>Michael Turner</name> </author> <category term="WAMP2025" /> <summary> Polybius Biotech are pleased to announce the deployment of PolyGen portable fusion generates across the WAMP2025 event site. How to play To play you simply need an RFID card. Most cards will work, although anything that generates a dynamic identifier such as mobile phones, WHY payment card or some bank cards will not work. Your objective is to keep as many of the units aligned to your team as... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>WHY2025 Game Results</title><link href="https://gen.polyb.io/posts/WHY2025Results/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WHY2025 Game Results" /><published>2025-08-12T15:00:00+01:00</published> <updated>2025-08-12T20:32:49+01:00</updated> <id>https://gen.polyb.io/posts/WHY2025Results/</id> <content src="https://gen.polyb.io/posts/WHY2025Results/" /> <author> <name>Michael Turner</name> </author> <category term="WHY2025" /> <summary> What Hackers Yearn 2025 is over and so we must analyse the stats from this year’s PolyGen game! General Stats Total players: 730 Total players scoring over 1,000 points: 496 Total players score: 8,732,428 Total unit captures: 13,902 Total unit visits: 14,292 Total output boosts: 2,501 Players who set a codename: 124 Players too lazy to set a codename: 606 Maximum Units Onli... </summary> </entry> </feed>
